

Tasnim Kibria Aurpa

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cell Number: +8801677875487 Date of Birth: 28th April, 1994

Email Address: tasnim.kibria.aurpa@gmail.com Address: 2/1 Monipuri Para, Tejgoan, Dhaka – 1215

Objective

Working with **3 years** of experience organizing presentations, preparing facility reports, writing contents, managing Facebook page and other social platforms, Boosting facebook posts, and maintaining the utmost confidentiality. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into Marketing related role.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Control, Executive Bproperty.com (May 14, 2017 to Present)

Job Responsibilities:

- Use database to research, gather, analyze and present data.
- Manage Data Collectors (DCs) for smooth work.
- Developed team communication and information DCs meeting.
- Researched and analyzed information into briefing papers, reports and project papers.
- Quality Assurance of each contents every day for developing website.

- Writing Marketing Content according to recent campaign.
- Working on Company's Control Panel (CP) for live content and internal project record.
- Developing Content writing for website according to product.
- Meeting the KPI which was assigned to me.
- Writing descriptive marketing contents.

Project Intern Eskayef Bangladesh Limited (SK+F) (January 2017 to April 2017)

Job Responsibilities:

- Doctors Special Relationship Report Analysis (DSR)
- Eskayef Marketing Research (EMR)
- 4p Monitoring
- Call plan (Olmesta & Rivarox)
- M-Reporting Analysis, Marketing Plan
- Presentation on EMR Report
- Campaign

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

- Master of Business Administration (M.B.A) from North South University, (2018 to Present) Major- Human Resource Management CGPA- 3.11 out of 4
- Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A) from North South University, (2012 to 2016) Majors-
 - Marketing
 - International Business

CGPA- 3.24 out of 4

- Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C) from Dhaka Commerce College, 2011 Business Studies GPA 4.90 out of 5
- Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C) from Chittagong Cantonment Public School, 2009
 Business Studies
 GPA- 5 out of 5

Key Skills

Project management Managing social platforms
Strong decision maker Knowledge about boosting social posts.
Writing article and blog Influenceing people

Reference- Iftekhar Kabir, Sourcing Management Specialist at General Electric.

Mobile: 01676986635 Email: iftekhar.kabir.ik@gmail.com